New England Archivists, Inc. Records 1992.0012
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Officers, 1969-1997
  - Subseries A: Presidents, 1969-1997
    - Rutherford Witthus, 2003-2004
      - Meeting--Fall, 2003 (Box 22:1015)
      - Meetings, 2004 (Box 22:1016)
      - Meeting--Spring, 2004 (Box 22:1017)
      - Meeting, 2004 June (Box 22:1018)
    - Mary Ide, 2004-2005 (Box 2013-0033)
      Scope and Content Note
      Records compiled by 2004-2005 NEA president Mary Ide, including board meeting and committee reports, 2001-2006; reports about branding (NEA's graphic identity), 2005; public relations, speeches given at meetings, and planning.
    - Paige Roberts, 2012
      - Quarterly board meeting (Redwood Library, Newport, Rhode Island), 2012 June 1 (Box 32)
      - Other reports for board meetings, 2012 July-December (Box 32)
  - Subseries B: Vice Presidents, 1995-1997
    - Conference planning, 1994-2007 (Box 31)
    - Executive Board Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 6:263)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996 (Box 6:264)
    - Files, 1995 (Box 6:265)
    - Local arrangements, 1999-2005 (Box 31)
    - Task Force on future Directions of NEA, 1996-1997 (Box 6:266)
  - Subseries C: Secretary, 1972-
    - Minutes
      - 1972 (Box 6:267)
      - 1973 (Box 6:268)
      - 1974 (Box 6:269)
      - 1975 (Box 6:270)
      - 1976 (Box 6:271)
      - 1977 (Box 6:272)
      - 1978 (Box 6:273)
      - 1979 January (Box 6:274)
      - 1979 April (Box 6:275)
      - 1979 June (Box 6:276)
      - 1979 November (Box 6:277)
      - 1980 January (Box 6:278)
      - 1980 Spring (Box 6:279)
      - 1980 April (Box 6:280)
      - 1980 June (Box 6:281)
      - 1980 September (Box 6:282)
      - 1980 October (Box 6:283)
      - 1981 January (Box 6:284)
      - 1981 May (Box 6:285-286)
      - 1981 July (Box 6:287)
      - 1981 October (Box 6:288)
      - 1982 January (Box 6:289)
      - 1982 May (Box 6:290-291)
      - 1982 July (Box 6:292)
      - 1982 October (Box 6:293)
      - 1983 January (Box 6:294)
      - 1983 April (Box 6:295-296)
      - 1983 June (Box 6:297)
      - 1983 November (Box 6:298)
      - 1984 January (Box 6:299)
      - 1984 April (Box 6:300-301)
      - 1984 June (Box 6:302)
      - 1984 November (Box 6:303)
      - 1995 February (Box 6:304)
      - 1985 May (Box 6:305-306)
      - 1985 June (Box 6:307)
      - 1985 October (Box 6:308)
      - 1986 January (Box 6:309)
      - 1986 April (Box 6:310-311)
      - 1986 June (Box 6:312)
      - 1986 October (Box 6:313)
      - 1987 January (Box 7:314)
      - 1987 May (Box 7:315-316)
      - 1987 July (Box 7:317)
      - 1987 October (Box 7:318)
      - 1988 January (Box 7:319)
      - 1988 March (Box 7:320-321)
      - 1988 July (Box 7:322)
      - 1988 October (Box 7:323)
      - 1989 January (Box 7:324)
      - 1989 March (Box 7:325)
      - 1989 April (Box 7:326)
      - 1989 June (Box 7:327)
      - 1989 November (Box 7:328)
      - 1990 January (Box 7:329)
      - 1990 April (Box 7:330-331)
      - 1990 July (Box 7:332)
      - 1990 October (Box 7:333)
      - 1991 January (Box 7:334)
      - 1991 April (Box 7:335-336)
      - 1991 July (Box 7:337)
      - 1991 November (Box 7:338)
      - 1992 January (Box 7:339)
      - 1992 April (Box 7:340-341)
      - 1992 June (Box 7:342)
      - 1992 November (Box 7:343)
      - 1993 January (Box 7:344)
      - 1993 October (Box 7:345)
      - 1994 January (Box 7:346)
      - 1994 April (Box 7:347-348)
      - 1995 October (Box 7:349)
      - 1996 February 2 (Box 7:350)
      - 1996 February 7 (Box 7:351)
      - 1996 April (Box 7:352)
      - 1996 July (Box 7:353)
      - 1996 October (Box 7:354)
      - 1997 February (Box 7:355)
      - 1997 April (Box 7:356-357)
      - 1997 July (Box 7:358)
      - 1997 October (Box 7:359)
      - 1998 January (Box 7:360)
      - 1998 April (Box 7:361-362)
      - 1998 July (Box 7:363)
      - 1998 October (Box 7:364)
      - 1999 January (Box 7:365)
      - 1999 April (Box 7:366)
      - 1999 April (Box 8:367)
      - 1999 July (Box 8:368)
      - 1999 November (Box 8:369)
      - 2000 February (Box 8:370)
      - 2000 April (Box 8:370a-370b)
      - 2000 July (Box 8:371-372)
      - 2000 October (Box 8:373)
      - 2001 January (Box 8:374-375)
      - 2001 May (Box 8:376-378)
      - 2001 July (Box 8:379-380)
      - 2001 October (Box 8:381-382)
      - 2002 January (Box 8:383)
      - 2002 April (Box 8:384)
    - 2004-2012 (Box 30)
      - 2004 March 26
      - 2004 March 27
      - 2004 June 17
      - 2004 October 15
      - 2005 January 19
      - 2005 April 29
      - 2005 April 30
      - 2005 May 25
      - 2005 June 29
      - 2005 October 14
      - 2006 January 17 (Box 31)
      - 2006 March 10 (Box 31)
      - 2006 March 11 (Box 31)
      - 2006 June 19 (Box 31)
      - 2006 October 20 (Box 31)
      - Wesleyan University, Middletown, Connecticut, 2012 March 23 (Box 32)
      - Contact lists; Policies and procedures manual, 2008 (Box 31)
    - Award Information (old), undated, 1988 (Box 8:385)
    - Candidacy, 1978 (Box 8:386)
    - Committee Information and forms (old), 1997-1998 (Box 8:387)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 8:388)
    - Directory, 1999 (Box 8:389)
    - Executive Board lists, 1989-1990 (Box 8:390)
    - Executive Board policies, 1973-1977 (Box 8:391)
    - Executive calendar, 1977 (Box 8:392)
    - Hale Award Certificate, undated (Box 8:393)
    - History of NEA meetings and elections (Desrochers), 1972-1988 (Box 8:394)
    - Honoraria payment guidelines, 1999 (Box 8:395)
    - Job descriptions, 2001-2002 (Box 8:396)
    - Mailing lists, undated, 1980 (Box 8:397)
    - NHPRC: effort to save, 1981 (Box 8:398)
    - Officier's biographies, 1974-1978 (Box 8:399)
    - Officer's accounts/receipts, 1973-1976 (Box 8:400)
    - Officer's correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 8:401)
    - Officer's correspondence, 1975 (Box 8:402)
    - Officer's correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 8:403)
    - Publicity, 1980 (Box 8:404)
    - Policy Manual, By-Laws, Job Description, 1986 (Box 8:405)
    - Procedural policies, undated, 1980-1981 (Box 8:406)
    - Records/Reports (Treasurer's), 1973-1975 (Box 8:407)
    - Records/Reports (Treasurer's), 1976 (Box 8:408)
  - Subseries D: Treasurer, 1973-
    General note
    [This subseries is arranged chronologically.]
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 8:409)
    - Reports, 1976-1981 (Box 8:410)
    - Reports, 1977 (Box 8:411)
    - Tax Exempt status, 1977 (Box 8:412)
    - Reports, 1978 (Box 8:413)
    - Reports, 1978 (Box 8:414)
    - Files, 1978 (Box 8:415)
    - Non-Profit status, 1978 (Box 8:416)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 8:417)
    - Files, 1979 (Box 8:418)
    - Reports, 1979 (Box 8:419)
    - Files, 1980 (Box 8:420-421)
    - Reports, 1980 (Box 8:422)
    - Files, 1981 (Box 8:423-424)
    - Report, 1981 (Box 8:425)
    - Reports, 1982 (Box 8:426)
    - Reports, 1982-1988 (Box 9:427)
    - Files, 1985 (Box 9:428)
    - Policies, 1985-1986 (Box 9:429)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 9:430)
    - Files, 1986 (Box 9:431)
    - Files, 1986, 1996 (Box 9:432)
    - Budget, 1987 (Box 9:433)
    - Files, 1987 (Box 9:434)
    - Financial matters, 1988 (Box 9:435)
    - Reports, 1988-1993 (Box 9:436)
    - Financial Statement review, 1993 (Box 9:437)
    - IRS, 1994 (Box 9:438)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 1995 (Box 9:439)
    - IRS, 1995 (Box 9:440)
    - Reports, 1995 (Box 9:441)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 1996 (Box 9:442)
    - Reports, 1996 (Box 9:443)
    - IRS, 1996 (Box 9:444)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 1997 (Box 9:445)
    - Reports, 1997 (Box 9:446)
    - Financial statement (unaudited), 1997 (Box 9:447)
    - Financial statement (unaudited), 1997-1998 (Box 9:448)
    - IRS, 1997 (Box 9:449)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 1998 (Box 9:450)
    - Reports, 1998 (Box 9:451)
    - Financial statement (unaudited), 1999 (Box 9:452)
    - IRS, 1998 (Box 9:453)
    - Financial statement (unaudited), 1999 (Box 9:454)
    - Tax Exempt certificate, 1999-2004 (Box 9:454a)
    - Richard L. Hass Memorial Award, 1991-1998 (Box 23:, Folder 1023)
    - Correspondence--tax filing problems, 1994-2001 (Box 23:, Folder 1024)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 1999 (Box 23:, Folder 1025)
    - Treasurer's Manual, 1999 (Box 23:, Folder 1026)
    - US Department of the Treasury, IRS, 1999 (Box 23:, Folder 1027)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 2000 (Box 23:, Folder 1028)
    - US Department of the Treasury, IRS, 2000 (Box 23:, Folder 1029)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 2001 (Box 23:, Folder 1030)
    - NEA Financial statements (unaudited), 2001 (Box 23:, Folder 1031)
    - US Department of the Treasury, IRS, 2001 (Box 23:, Folder 1032)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 2002 (Box 23:, Folder 1033)
    - Treasurer's records, 2001-2005 (Box 30)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 1034)
    - NEA Financial statements (unaudited), 2002 (Box 23:, Folder 1035)
    - US Department of the Treasury, IRS, 2002 (Box 23:, Folder 1036)
    - MA Office of the Attorney General, 2003 (Box 23:, Folder 1037)
    - NEA Financial statements (unaudited), 2003 (Box 23:, Folder 1038)
    - Treasurer's reports, 2003 (Box 23:, Folder 1039)
    - US Department of the Treasury, IRS, 2003 (Box 23:, Folder 1040)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 2004 (Box 23:, Folder 1041)
    - Federal and State forms, 2005 (Box 23:, Folder 1042)
    - Treasurer's Manual, 2005 April (Box 23:, Folder 1043)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 2005 (Box 23:, Folder 1044)
    - Treasurer's records, 2007-2009 (Box 30)
    - Treasurer's records (Maria Bernier), 2009-2013 (Box 32)
    - Report (2012 January 1-August 13) (Box 32)
  - Subseries E: Representatives At Large, (1978-1990)
    - 1978 (Box 9:455)
    - 1982 (Box 9:456)
    - 1983 (Box 9:457)
    - 1984 (Box 9:458)
    - 1985 (Box 9:459)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 9:460)
  - Rick Stattler (Representative at large, Spring 2002 Local arrangements chair), 2000-2002 (Box 26)
    - Brochures, undated
    - Spring meeting follow up and reports, 2002
    - Spring evaluations, 2002
    - Spring local arrangements, 2002
    - Spring Program, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--Board meeting, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--packet stuffing, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--registration (3 ff), 2002
    - Local Arrangements--program committee, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--Hotel, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--catering, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--raffle, 2002
    - Local Arrangements--committee, 2002
    - Outreach (7 ff), 1998-2001
    - Board (20 ff), 2000
    - Administrative handbook, undated
  - Subseries F: Newsletter Editor, (1972-1994)
    - General, 1972-1976 (Box 9:461)
    - Other Associations, 1972-1975 (Box 9:462)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 9:463)
    - 1976 (Box 9:464)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 9:465)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 9:466)
    - 1978 (Box 9:467-469)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 9:470)
    - 1979 (Box 9:471-476)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9:477)
    - 1980 (Box 9:478-479)
    - Reprint permission, 1986 (Box 9:480)
    - 1986 (Box 9:481)
    - Editor's files (25 ff), undated, 1990-1998 (Box 30)
    - Rules and regulations, 1994 (Box 9:482)
    - Handbook, 2003 (Box 30)
  - Subseries G: Print Coordinator, (1994-)
    - Ballot, 1994 (Box 9:483)
    - Ballot, 1997 (Box 9:484)
    - Ballot, 1998 (Box 10:485)
    - Ballot, 1999 (Box 10:486)
    - Ballot, 2001 (Box 10:487)
    - Ballot, 2002 (Box 10:488)
    - Ballot, 2003 (Box 10:489)
    - Ballot and meeting program, 2004 (Box 22:1009)
    - Ballot and meeting program, 2005 (Box 22:1022)
    - Logo Search, 1991-1993 (Box 10:490)
    - Membership Brochure, 2001 (Box 10:491)
    - Print Coordinator, 1990-1992 (Box 10:492)
    - Print Samples, undated (Box 10:493)
    - Working File, 1993-1994 (Box 10:494)
- Series III: Meeting Files, 1973-
  - Spring, 1973 (Box 10:495)
  - Fall, 1973 (Box 10:496)
  - Spring, 1974 (Box 10:497)
  - Fall, 1974 (Box 10:498)
  - Spring, 1975 (Box 10:499)
  - Spring, 1975 (Box 15:781)
  - Fall, 1975 (Box 10:500-501)
  - Spring, 1976 (Box 10:502)
  - Fall, 1976 (Box 10:503)
  - Fall, 1976 (Box 15:782)
  - Spring, 1977 (Box 10:504)
  - Fall, 1977 (Box 10:505)
  - Spring, 1978 (Box 10:506)
  - Spring, 1978 (Box 15:783)
  - Fall, 1978 (Box 10:507)
  - Spring, 1979 (Box 10:508)
  - Fall, 1979 (Box 10:509)
  - Spring, 1980 (Box 10:510)
  - Fall, 1980 (Box 10:511-515)
  - Fall, 1980 (Box 15:784)
  - Committee, 1981-1994 (Box 15:785)
  - Spring, 1981 (Box 10:516)
  - Fall, 1981 (Box 10:517)
  - Spring, 1982 (Box 10:518-519)
  - Fall, 1983 (Box 11:520-521)
  - Spring, 1984 (Box 11:522)
  - Fall, 1984 (Box 11:523)
  - Spring, 1985 (Box 11:524)
  - Fall, 1985 (Box 11:525-526)
  - Spring, 1986 (Box 11:527)
  - Fall, 1986 (Box 11:528-529)
  - Spring, 1987 (Box 11:530)
  - Fall, 1987 (Box 11:531)
  - Spring, 1988 (Box 11:532-548)
  - Fall, 1988 (Box 11:549)
  - Spring, 1989 (Box 11:550)
  - Fall, 1989 (Box 11:551)
  - Spring, 1990 (Box 11:552)
  - Fall, 1990 (Box 11:553)
  - Spring, 1991 (Box 11:554)
  - Fall, 1991 (Box 11:555-556)
  - Spring, 1992 (Box 11:557-559)
  - Fall, 1992 (Box 11:560-562)
  - Spring, 1993 (Box 11:563-567)
  - Fall, 1993 (Box 11:568-575)
  - Fall, 1993 (Box 12:576)
  - Fall, 1993 (Box 12:577-578)
  - Spring, 1994 (Box 12:579-586)
  - Fall, 1994 (Box 12:587-589)
  - Fall, 1995 (Box 12:590)
  - Spring, 1996 (Box 12:591)
  - Spring, 1996 (Box 15:786)
  - Spring, 1997 (Box 12:592)
  - Fall, 1997 (Box 12:593)
  - Spring, 1998 (Box 12:594)
  - Fall, 1998 (Box 12:595-597)
  - Spring, 1999 (Box 12:598)
  - Spring, 2000 (Box 12:599-600)
  - Spring, 2001 (Box 12:601)
  - Fall, 2001 (Box 12:602)
  - Spring, 2002 (Box 12:603)
  - Spring, 2003 (Box 12:604)
  - Fall, 2003 (Box 21:993)
  - Spring--Evaluations, 2004 (Box 22:1021)
  - Spring (2ff), 2006 (Box 30)
  - Fall (2ff), 2007 (Box 31)
  - Fall (meeting at Simmons College, Boston, Massachusetts), registration postcard, 2012 (Box 32)
- Series IV: Committees, 1972-
  - [This subseries is arranged chronologically.]
  - Archives Week, 1987-1988 (Box 12:605)
  - Archives Week, 2003 (Box OS)
  - By-laws Revision
    - 1977-1980 (Box 12:606)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 12:607)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 12:608)
  - Constitution, 1973 (Box 12:609)
  - Education
    - 1974 (Box 12:610)
    - 1978 (Box 12:611)
    - Final report, 1979 (Box 12:612)
    - General (Box 12:613-614)
    - Plenary session, 1979 (Box 12:615)
    - Questionnaire, 1979 (Box 12:616-617)
    - 1980 (Box 12:618)
    - 1983-1990 (Box 13:620)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 12:619)
    - Education Project, 1988-1990 (Box 13:621)
    - Education Project: Advisory Board, 1988-1990 (Box 13:622)
    - Job Descriptions, 1989 (Box 13:623)
    - 1989, 1990, 1995 (Box 13:624)
    - Education Project, 1989-1990 (Box 13:625)
    - 1990-1994 (Box 13:626)
    - Handbook, 1991 (Box 13:627)
    - 1993 (Box 13:628)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 13:629)
    - , circa 1994 (Box 29)
    - Future Directions Task Force, 1995 (Box 13:630)
    - Long Range Plan, 1995 (Box 13:631)
    - 1995 (Box 13:632-633)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 13:634)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 13:635)
    - Archival Education report, 1996 (Box 13:636)
    - Honoraria, 1996 (Box 13:637)
    - 1996 (Box 13:638-643)
    - Certification, 1997 (Box 13:644)
    - Job Description, 1997 (Box 13:645)
    - 1997 (Box 13:646-650)
    - Members, 1997-1999 (Box 13:651)
    - Planning Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 13:652)
    - Budgets, 1997-2001 (Box 13:653)
    - Inside NEA, 1997-1999 (Box 13:654)
    - 1997-2001 (Box 13:656)
    - By-Laws, 1998 (Box 13:657)
    - 1998 (Box 13:658)
    - Notebook Inserts, 2000 (Box 13:659)
    - SAA-NEA, 2000 (Box 13:660)
    - Agendas, 2001-2003 (Box 13:661)
    - Boards reports, 2001-2003 (Box 13:662)
    - Budgets, 2001-2003 (Box 13:663)
    - Membership, 2002 (Box 13:664)
    - Minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 13:665)
    - Workshops
      - Evaluation forms, undated (Box 13:666)
      - Proposals, undated (Box 13:667)
      - SAA course survey of NEA members, undated (Box 13:668)
      - 1974 (Box 13:669-670)
      - 1975 (Box 13:671)
      - 1976 (Box 13:672)
      - 1977 (Box 13:673)
      - 1980 (Box 13:674-675)
      - 1981 (Box 13:676-678)
      - 1982 (Box 13:679-680)
      - Workshops, 1982-1994 (Box 13:681)
      - 1985 (Box 13:682)
      - 1986 (Box 13:683)
      - Evaluations and schedules, 1986, 1980-1988 (Box 13:684)
      - 1987 (Box 13:685)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 13:686)
      - 1989 (Box 13:687-688)
      - Workshop Descriptions, 1989-2002 (Box 13:689)
      - Workshop retrospective, 1989-1999 (Box 13:690)
      - 1990 (Box 13:691)
      - 1991 (Box 13:692-695)
      - 1992 (Box 13:696-698)
      - 1992 (Box 14:699-707)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 14:708-709)
      - 1993 (Box 14:710-718)
      - Evaluations, 1992-1993 (Box 14:719)
      - 1994 (Box 14:720-721)
      - 1995 (Box 14:722)
      - 1996 (Box 14:723)
      - 1997 (Box 13:655)
      - 1998 (Box 14:724)
      - 1998-2001 (Box 14:725)
      - 1999 (Box 14:726-727)
      - 2000 (Box 14:728)
      - 2001 (Box 14:729)
      - 2002 (Box 30)
      - 2004 (Box 31)
      - 2005 (Box 31)
      - 2006 (Box 30)
      - 2007 (Box 30)
      - 2008 (Box 30)
      - 2009 (Box 30)
      - 2010 (Box 30)
      - Planning checklist, 2001-2003 (Box 14:730)
      - Workshop evaluations, 2003 Fall (Box 21:992)
      - Workshop evaluations--Digital Assets Management, 2005 Spring (Box 23:, Folder 1045)
      - Arrangement and Description, 2011 May 20 (Box 30)
      - Arrangement and Description, 2011 October 24 (Box 30)
  - Hale Award, 1983-
    - Certificates, undated (Box 14:731)
    - 1983 (Box 14:732)
    - 1984 (Box 14:733)
    - 1985 (Box 14:734)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 14:735)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 14:736)
    - 1986 (Box 14:737)
    - 1987 (Box 14:738)
    - 1988 (Box 14:739)
    - 1989 (Box 14:740-741)
    - 1990 (Box 14:742-743)
    - 1991 (Box 14:744-748)
    - 1992 (Box 14:749)
    - 1993 (Box 14:750)
    - 1994 (Box 14:751)
    - 1995 (Box 14:752)
    - 1996 (Box 14:753)
    - 1997 (Box 14:754)
    - 1998 (Box 14:755)
    - 1999 (Box 14:756-757)
  - Local Arrangements
    - Committee records (7 ff), 2003 Fall (Box 31)
    - Report, 2003 Fall (Box 21:996)
    - Handbook, 1994-1994 (Box 21:997)
    - Spring 1996 Meeting Files, 1995-1996
      - Committee Files (Box 23:, Folder 1048)
      - Committee Files (Box 24:, Folder 1049-1050)
      - Computer Needs (Box 24:, Folder 1051)
      - Expenses (Box 24:, Folder 1052)
      - Facilities (Box 24:, Folder 1053)
      - Final Report, 1996 July 12 (Box 24:, Folder 1054)
      - General (Box 24:, Folder 1055)
      - Honoraria, Travel, Complimentary Registration (Box 24:, Folder 1056)
      - Maps/Floor plans (Box 24:, Folder 1057)
      - Meeting Announcement (Box 24:, Folder 1058)
      - Museum Computer Network, New England Chapter (Box 24:, Folder 1059)
      - Program (Box 24:, Folder 1060)
      - Registration Packet (Box 25:, Folder 1061-1063)
      - Schedule (Box 25:, Folder 1064)
      - Vendors--Accepted (Box 25:, Folder 1965)
      - Vendors--Background (Box 25:, Folder 1066)
      - Vendors--Working file (Box 25:, Folder 1067)
      - Workshops/Education Committee (Box 25:, Folder 1068)
      - Workshops--Processing Fundamentals (Box 25:, Folder 1069)
      - Workshops--Automating Finding Guides (Box 25:, Folder 1070)
      - Workshops--Automating Finding Guides (2nd) (Box 25:, Folder 1071)
  - Long Range Planning, 1987-1995
    - Charge/Mission/Policy statement (Box 14:758)
    - Correspondence (Box 14:759)
    - Forms (Box 14:760)
    - GAP report (Box 14:761)
    - Meetings (Box 14:762)
    - Members (Box 14:763)
    - Memoranda (Box 14:764)
    - Plans (Box 14:765)
    - Reports (Box 14:766)
  - Membership, 1970-
    - Brochure, 2005 (Box 23:, Folder 1047)
    - Directory, 1976 (Box 15:794)
    - Directory, 1978 (Box 15:795)
    - Directory, 1982 (Box 15:796)
    - Directory, 1983 (Box 15:797)
    - Directory, 1989 (Box 15:798)
    - Directory, 1991 (Box 15:799)
    - Directory, 1993-1996 (Box 15:800)
    - Directory, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
    - Directory, 1996-1997 (Box 29)
    - Directory, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Directories: regional, 1974-1977 (Box 15:801)
    - Flyers, undated (Box 15:802)
    - Membership list, 1973 (Box 15:803)
    - Membership list, 1974 (Box 15:804)
    - Membership list, 1975 (Box 15:805)
    - Membership list, 1978 (Box 15:806)
    - Publications: Public Records Repositories in Maine (Box 15:807)
    - Publications: SAA Directory, 1970 (Box 15:808)
    - Publications: SAA Directory, 1976 (Box 15:809)
    - Publications: SAA Directory/ NEA Directory, 1978 (Box 15:810)
    - Publicity, 1976 (Box 15:811)
    - Recordkeeping, undated (Box 15:812)
    - Survey, 1986 (Box 15:813)
    - Survey of Membership, 1992 (Box 15:814-817)
    - Survey of Membership, 1992 (Box 16:818-820)
    - Survey: New Membership, 1986 (Box 16:821)
  - Nominating, 1975-
    - Election, 1975 (Box 16:822)
    - Election, 1976 (Box 16:823)
    - Election, 1977 (Box 16:824)
    - Election, 1978 (Box 16:825)
    - Election, 1979 (Box 16:826)
    - Election, 1980 (Box 16:827)
    - Election, 1981 (Box 16:828)
    - Election, 1982 (Box 16:829)
    - Election, 1983 (Box 16:830)
    - Election, 1984 (Box 16:831)
    - Election, 1985 (Box 15:767)
    - Election, 1985-1986 (Box 15:772)
    - Election, 1986-1987 (Box 15:768)
    - Election, 1988 (Box 15:769)
    - Election, 1988 (Box 15:773)
    - Election, 1989 (Box 15:774)
    - Election, 1990-1997 (Box 15:775)
    - Election, 1997-1998 (Box 15:770)
    - Election History, 1972-1988 (Box 15:771)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 15:776-777)
    - Election, 2004 (Box 22:1008)
  - Outreach
    - 1986 (Box 15:778)
    - 1988 (Box 15:779)
    - 1990 (Box 15:780)
    - Committee records, 2004 (Box 31)
  - Program
    - Co-Chair Files, 2001 Fall (Box 22:1019-1020)
    - Publicity, 2003 Fall (Box 21:994)
    - Report, 2003 Fall (Box 21:995)
    - Chair's files for Spring 2012 meeting at Wesleyan University in Middletown, Connecticut, 2010-2012 (Box 32)
  - Public Records, 1982 (Box 15:787)
  - Public Relations, 1989-1993 (Box 15:788)
  - Steering
    - 1972-1974 (Box 15:789)
    - 1973 (Box 15:790)
  - Subcommittees, 1995 (Box 15:791)
  - Task Force on Society, 1986 (Box 15:792)
  - Task Force on Future Directions
    - 1995-1996 (Box 16:832)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 15:793)
  - Web Committee
    - 2002 (Box 22:998)
    - 2002 August - September (Box 22:1001)
    - 2002 October - November (Box 22:999)
    - Images, 2001 (Box 22:1001)
    - Images--permissions, 2001 (Box 22:1002)
- Series V: Subject Files, undated, 1977-
  - Administrative Assistant, 1995-1996 (Box 16:833)
  - Archives Week Proclamation (NH), 1989 (Box 20)
  - Big E exhibition, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 29)
  - Board electronic mail, 1999-2000 (Box 16:836-856)
  - Board electronic mail, 2000-2002 (Box 17:857-877)
  - Brochure, undated (Box 16:834-835)
  - Brochure, undated (Box 17:878-879)
  - Calendar, 1979 (Box 17:880)
  - Connecticut Historical Records Repositories, 1982-1983 (Box 17:881)
  - Dismissal of MA State Archivist, 1995 (Box 17:882)
  - Financial Audit, 1996 (Box 17:883)
  - Goals and Priorities, 1985-1986 (Box 17:884)
  - Grant application (Basic workshop), 1986 (Box 17:885)
  - Hale Award, 1985-1986, 1996 (Box 17:886)
  - Letterhead, undated (Box 17:887)
  - Mailing list, 1987 (Box 17:888)
  - Meeting Index, 1994-2001 (Box 17:889)
  - Meeting Files (Members' copies), 1986-1992 (Box 17:890-893)
  - National Archives, 1979-1980 (Box 18:895)
  - NEA Book, undated, 1993-1996 (Box 18:896-908)
  - NEA Distinguished Service Award, undated (Box 18:909)
  - NEA Logo, undated (Box 18:910)
  - NEA/MARAC Publication, 1982-1983 (Box 18:894)
  - Public Relations, 1986 (Box 18:911)
  - Publications and Mailings, 1977-1978 (Box 18:912)
  - Publications and Mailings, 1980 (Box 18:913)
  - Regional Repositories Guide Project, 1995 (Box 18:914)